Ireland
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Ireland
2.1.1.1.12
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1188
- Ireland, 2.1.1.1.12
  - Giants Causeway looking toward sea, 1912 August 1; 85; 21011; 927; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Giants Causeway, old lady and wishing well, 1912 August 1; 86; 21012; 919; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Honeycomb formation, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 87; 21013; 920; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - General view, honeycomb formation, Giants causeway, 1912 August 1; 88; 21014; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Chimney tops, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 89; 21016; 926; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in the wishing chair, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 90; 21018; 922; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  Box 1189
- Ireland, 2.1.1.1.12
  - Lord Antrun’s parlor, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 1; 21019; 923; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Giants loom, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 2; 21020; 925; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Grand Causeway, Giants Causeway, 1912 August 1; 3; 21021; 928; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - “Glynn” village near Larne, 1912 August 1; 4; 21000; 912; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - City Hall, Belfast, 1912 August 1; 5; 21001; 913; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - City Hall with statue of Queen Victoria, Belfast, 1912 August 1; 6; 21002; 914; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Monuments in front of City Hall, Belfast, 1912 August 1; 7; 21003; 915; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Chickens in cart, near Belfast, 1912 August 1; 8; 21004; 916; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Lakes from Glengariff Road, close-up, near Killarney, 1912 August 1; 9; 21092; 991; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Peat bogs, showing stacking, North Ireland, 1912 August 1; 10; 21007; 16-918; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Peat bogs, small stacks, North Ireland, 1912 August 1; 11; 21008; 918; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Peat bogs along roadside, Frank R. Roberson, North Ireland, 1912 August 1; 12; 21009; 14-918; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Peat stored along roadside, with automobile, North Ireland, 1912 August 1; 13; 21010; 15-918; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Child on haystack, North Ireland, 1912 August 2; 14; 21035; 939; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Load of peat, near Drumcliff, 1912 August 2; 15; 21037; 940; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Hayfield in front of mountain, near Drumcliff, 1912 August 2; 16; 21038; 941; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Hayfield near Drumcliff, 1912 August 2; 17; 21039; 942; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Scenic, Killary Harbor near clifden, road to recess, 1912 August 2; 18; 21041; 944; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road, Killary Harbor and sheep, on Slego to Recess, 1912 August 2; 19; 21042; 945; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Bough near Clifden Connemara, 1912 August 2; 20; 21043; 946; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Barnesmore gap and lake, 1912 August 2; 21; 21027; 933; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Barnesmore farm house, 1912 August 2; 22; 21028; 934; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Countryside view, near Stranorlar, 1912 August 2; 23; 21023; 930; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Heather, 1912 August 2; 24; 21025; 932; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Neplain mountain near Westport, Northwestern Ireland, 1912 August 2; 25; 21040; 943; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Lakes from Glengariff Road, taken from hillside, Killarney, 1912 August 2; 26; 21098; 998; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Kylemore Castle near Letterfrack County Connemara, 1912 August 4; 27; 21044; 947; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - View of Lough and mountains at Recess, 1912 August 4; 28; 21045; 948; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road scene near Limerick, 1912 August 4; 29; 21046; 949; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - General view of River Shannon with old castle, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 30; 21047; 950; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Looking down the River Shannon, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 31; 21048; 951; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Castle from bridge, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 32; 21049; 952; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Towers of King John’s Castle, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 33; 21050; 953; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Patrick Street, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 34; 21051; 955; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Patrick Street from Crescent, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 35; 21052; 956; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Perry Square, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 36; 21053; 957; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson sitting in cart, 1912 August 5; 37; 21054; 958; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - St. Mary’s Cathedral, Limerick, 1912 August 5; 38; 21169; 954; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Pastoral scene near Killarney, 1912 August 5; 39; 21055; 959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Close-up of Muckross Abbey, Killarney, 1912 August 5; 40; 21056; 23-959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road scene in Barnesmore Gap, 1912 August 6; 41; 21029; 935; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road scene and view of Barnesmore Gap, 1912 August 6; 42; 21030; 10-935; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Mountains and road, Barnesmore Gap, 1912 August 6; 43; 21031; 11-935; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - View of Muckross Lake from drive, Killarney, 1912 August 6; 44; 21057; 959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Brickeen Bridge between middle and lower lakes, Killarney, 1912 August 6; 45; 21060; 959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Muckross Abbey, general view with graveyard, Killarney, 1912 August 6; 46; 21061; 22-959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Street scene, village of Killarney, 1912 August 6; 47; 21062; 962; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Man standing in doorway of small cottages in village of Killarney, 1912 August 6; 48; 21063; 962; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Lower Lake and island, Killarney, 1912 August 6; 49; 21065; 959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Bawn Rock, Muckross Lake, Frank R. Roberson[?] looking at rocks in lake, 1912 August 6; 50; 21074; 959; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road scene near Ballyshannon, 1912 August 7; 51; 21031; 936; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Hayfields with children near Drumcliff, 1912 August 7; 52; 21034; 938; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Road scene along Lower Lake to village, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 53; 21064; 963; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Muckross Abbey, distant view, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 54; 21066; 965; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Detail of interior of Muckross Abbey, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 55; 21067; 966; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  - Lough leave or Lower Lake, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 56; 21068; 967; 5x7 (Box 1189)
  Box 1190
- Ireland, 2.1.1.1.12
  - Road along Lower Lake, Muckross Estate, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 1; 21070; 968; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - View of Lower Lake under trees, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 2; 21071; 970; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Lough leave or Lower Lake and sheep, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 3; 21072; 964; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Colonel Vincent’s home, Muckross Estate, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 4; 21073; 971; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Colleen Baun, rock under trees, Middle Lake, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 5; 21075; 972; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Looking down Muckross Lake toward Tore Mountains, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 6; 21076; 973; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Looking up to Weir Bridge and the meeting of the water, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 7; 21077; 974; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Heather, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 8; 21079; 976; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Heather, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 9; 21080; 977; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Ross Castle from road, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 10; 21081; 979; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Close-up of Ross Castle, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 11; 21082; 980; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Road to Glengariff, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 12; 21083; 981; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Where the Upper Lake enters the Long Range, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 13; 21085; 984; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Road scene to Glengariff near Killarney, 1912 August 8; 14; 21086; 978; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Road to Glengariff along Upper Lake, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 15; 21087; 980; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Upper Lake, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 16; 21088; 982; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Upper Lake and Arbutus Island, Killarney, 1912 August 8; 17; 21089; 987; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Upper Lake looking toward purple mountains, Killarney Lake, 1912 August 8; 18; 21090; 985; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Tunnel and auto on road along Upper Lake, Killarney[?], 1912 August 8; 19; 21091; 988; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - General view of Killarney Lakes, 1912 August; 20; 21093; 993; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Frank R. Rosenberg looking at lakes, picture taken from Glengariff Road, 1912 August; 21; 21094; 994; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Old Wair Bridge, between Lower and Middle Lake, Killarney Lake, 1912 August; 22; 21095; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - From Glengariff Road looking over Upper Lake, Killarney Lakes, 1912 August; 23; 21096; 989; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - From Glengariff Road, Killarney Lakes, 1912 August; 24; 21097; 990; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Upper Lake and gap of Dunloe, Killarney, 1912 August; 25; 21099; 995; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Lakes from top of Glengariff Road, general view, 1912 August; 26; 21100; 996; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Sunset on lake from Glengariff Road, 1912 August; 27; 21101; 997; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Street scene, Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 28; 21122; 1015; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - American training ship “Adams”, Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 29; 21124; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Jauntry car, car with feet supports turned up, near Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 30; 21125; 1018; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Jauntry car, car ready to start, near Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 31; 21126; 1017; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Jauntry car, rear view of car ready to start, near Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 32; 21127; 1019; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Jauntry car, car itself in resting position, near Queenstown, 1912 August 10; 33; 21128; 1020; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Large portrait of Irish child, County Donegal, 1912 August; 34; 21036; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Old Stone bridge between Bantry and Cork, 1912 August; 35; 21102; 998; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Old bridge near Bantry, between Bantry and Cork, 1912 August; 36; 21103; 999; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Kilkenny Castle on the Nore River, Kilkenny, 1912 August; 37; 21104; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Frank R. Roberson in a quaint corner in Kilkenny, steps leading to St. Canie’s Cathedral, Kilkenny, 1912 August; 38; 21106; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Old castle on River Brandon, near Cork, 1912 August; 39; 21108; 1000; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Road along River Brandon, near Cork, 1912 August; 40; 21109; 1001; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - St. Finn Barr Cathedral, Cork, 1912 August; 41; 21110; 1002; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Detail of doorway, Barr Cathedral, Cork, 1912 August; 42; 21111; 1003; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Shandon Church, Cork, 1912 August; 43; 21112; 1004; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Road to Blarney, near Cork, 1912 August; 44; 21113; 1005; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Frank R. Roberson looking at the Blarney Stone, 1912 August; 45; 21114; 1006; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Blarney Castle, parapet from which the stone is reached, Blarney, 1912 August; 46; 21115; 1007; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Blarney Castle through the trees, Blarney, 1912 August; 47; 21116; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Blarney Castle and location of Blarney Stone, 1912 August; 48; 21118; 1009; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Old Tower near Blarney, 1912 August; 49; 21120; 1011; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - The Keep, Blarney Castle, 1912 August; 50; 21121; 1012; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Lighthouse, Youghal, 1912 August; 51; 21129; 1021; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  - Clock tower on Main Street, Youghal, 1912 August; 52; 21130; 1022; 5x7 (Box 1190)
  Box 1191
- Ireland, 2.1.1.1.12
  - Cromwell Gate, Youghal, 1912 August; 1; 21131; 1023; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Up Blackwater, near Youghal, 1912 August; 2; 21132; 1024; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Keep of fortress of Temple Michael, along the Blackwater, 1912 August; 3; 21133; 1025; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Road view, near the Blackwater, 1912 August; 4; 21134; 1026; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Detail of Ash foliage and fruit near the Blackwater, 1912 August; 5; 21135; 1027; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - On the Blackwater near Youghal, 1912 August; 6; 21136; 1028; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Lismore Castle from road, Lismore, 1912 August; 7; 21137; 1029; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Lismore Castle side view from Gardens, Lismore, 1912 August; 8; 21138; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Lismore Castle from the bridge, Lismore, 1912 August; 9; 21139; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Lismore Castle and the Blackwater, Lismore, 1912 August; 10; 21140; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - The Blackwater at Lismore, 1912 August; 11; 21142; 1042; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - The Blackwater near Lismore, 1912 August; 12; 21143; 1033; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Entrance to Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 13; 21144; 1034; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Main gate of Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 14; 21145; 1035-21; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Garden, Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 15; 21146; 1036; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Lismore Castle, vertical view, 1912 August; 16; 21148; 1038; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Looking down the Blackwater from Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 17; 21149; 1042; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Looking up the Blackwater from Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 18; 21150; 1041; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - View of Blackwater and country from top of Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 19; 21152; 1043; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Down the Blackwater from top of Lismore Castle, 1912 August; 20; 21153; 1044; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Reginald’s Tower, Waterford, 1912 August; 21; 21154; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Moore’s tree in Vale of Avoca, 1912 August; 22; 21156; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Bridge near the “Meeting of the water, Vale of Avoca, 1912 August; 23; 21157; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Road in Vale of Avoca, 1912 August; 24; 21158; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Bray’s Head, Bray near Dublin, 1912 August; 25; 21159; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Sackville Street with Nelson Monument, Dublin, 1912 August; 26; 21160; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Sackville Street looking toward Nelson Monument, Dublin, 1912 August; 27; 21161; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Royal bank of Ireland, Dublin, 1912 August; 28; 21162; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Monument to O’Connell, Dublin, 1912 August; 29; 21163; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Statue of Gough in Phoenix Park, Dublin, 1912 August; 30; 21164; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Wellington Column, Phoenix Park, Dublin, 1912 August; 31; 21165; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Phoenix Column, Phoenix Park, Dublin, 1912 August; 32; 21166; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Parnell Statue, Dublin, 1912 August; 33; 21167; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Custom House, Dublin, 1912 August; 34; 21168; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Chapel Royal, Dublin, copy, before 1913; 35; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Colleen Bawn Caves, Killarney, copy, before 1913; 36; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Cottage, Killarney, copy, before 1913; 37; U; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Tunnel near Glengarriff, copy, before 1913; 38; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Peep hole, Blarney, copy, before 1913; 39; X; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Church Street, Enniskillen, copy, before 1913; 40; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Turf bog, Ballymena, copy, before 1913; 41; E; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Turf bog, Ballymena, copy, before 1913; 42; 7; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Linen bleach green, copy, before 1913; 43; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Linen bleach green, copy, before 1913; 44; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Crom Castle ruins, Loucherne, copy, before 1913; 45; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Strawberry beds, copy, before 1913; 46; T; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Cottages, copy, before 1913; 47; AA; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Crowd of people in streets, copy, before 1913; 48; Y; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Men in boat under bridge, copy, before 1913; 49; Z; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - View of castle through archway, copy, 1912 December; 50; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Low back car, copy, before 1913; 51; B; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Fair and easy goes far in a day, copy, before 1913; 52; D; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  - Man standing in cart, copy, before 1913; 53; G; 5x7 (Box 1191)
  Box 1192
- Ireland, 2.1.1.1.12
  - Man in chair reading, copy, before 1913; 1; H; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Old man in chair, copy, before 1913; 2; I; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Vegetable women, copy, before 1913; 3; J; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Man on stool with stick, copy, before 1913; 4; K; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Killarney colleen, copy, before 1913; 5; M; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Lily of Killarney, copy, before 1913; 6; N; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - She spins while fancy weaves, copy, before 1913; 7; O; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - An Irish colleen, copy, before 1913; 8; P; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Irish black thorns, copy, before 1913; 9; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - The Coleen bawn, copy, before 1913; 10; S; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Irish colleen, copy, before 1913; 11; BB; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Donegal cottage industries, sprigging and lace making, copy, before 1913; 12; CC; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Three dogs, copy, before 1913; 13; A; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Man and sheep on road, copy, before 1913; 14; C; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Pack of dogs on hill, copy, before 1913; 15; L; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Big dog, copy, before 1913; 16; R; 5x7 (Box 1192)
  - Sheep, copy, before 1913; 17; VV; 5x7 (Box 1192)